LISTENING, READING, AND SPEAKING
5.
Now read more about Freddy's life.
Freddy the Frog Part 2
Not long after Freddy and the band became famous, they visited Britain on a brief tour.
Fans showed their devotion by waiting for hours to get tickets
for their concerts.
Freddy was now quite confident when he went into a concert hall.
He enjoyed singing and all the congratulations afterwards!
It felt very strange.
Everybody was asking when they could see Freddy and his band again.
They were truly stars.
Then things went wrong.
Freddy and his band could not go out anywhere without being followed.
Even when they wore sunglasses or beards people recognized them.
Fans found them even when they went into the toilet.
They tried to hide in the reading rooms of libraries,
but it was useless.
Someone was always there!
Their personal life was regularly discussed by people who did not know them
but talked as if they were close friends.
At last feeling very upset and sensitive,
Freddy and his band realized that they must leave the country
before it became too painful for them.
So they left Britain, to which they were never to return,
and went back to the lake.